有庆祝活动吗  大家怎么庆祝的
Is there any entertainment there? What are people doing?
好的  过新年啦  1999年  乔伊年
All right! Here we go! 1999! The year of Joey!
真替你高兴
We're very happy for you.
怎么了
What's the matter?!
我们想在午夜时接吻
We wanted to kiss at midnight,
但其他人都没这个打算
but nobody else is going to so y'know...
好的  交给我了
All right, I'll take care of it.
等等  乔伊
Oh no, wait! Joey!
三十三  三十二  三十一
33, 32, 31...
罗斯  午夜时你想亲谁
Ross! Ross! Ross, listen! Who are you kissing at midnight, huh?
-瑞秋还是菲比  -什么
- Rachel or Phoebe? - What?
你得亲个人啊  你又不能亲你妹妹
Well you gotta kiss someone, you can't kiss your sister.
那谁要亲我妹
Well, who's gonna kiss my sister.
钱德勒
Chandler.
不会吧
Awww, man! Really?
兄弟  你觉得谁亲你妹更好
Dude-dude, who would you rather have kiss your sister,
-我还是钱德勒  -有道理
- me or Chandler? - That's a good point.
我和瑞秋有太多纠葛  那就菲比吧
Oh well, since I have that whole history with Rachel, I guess Phoebe.
好的
Okay, great.
菲比  罗斯午夜时想亲你
Pheebs! Pheebs! Listen, Ross wants to kiss you at midnight!
太明显了  他干嘛不直接问我
It's so obvious, why doesn't he just ask?
瑞秋  我午夜时要亲你
Rach! Rach! Listen, I'm gonna kiss you at midnight.
-什么  -新年就得这样
- What?! - Well, everyone's gotta kiss someone.
你不能亲罗斯  你们有前科
You can't kiss Ross you got the history.
所以呢
So?
所以你想让谁亲  我还是钱德勒
So? Who would you rather have kiss you, me or Chandler?
有道理
Oh, good point.
三  二  一
3! 2! 1!
新年快乐
Happy New Year!!
Happy New Year!
新年快乐
Happy New Year.
新年快乐  菲比
Happy New Year, Pheebs!
你也是
You too!
乔伊  新年快乐
Happy New Year, Joey!
刚才那个吻有感觉吗
So did that do anything for ya?
你们知道吗  我要大胆说一句
Y'know what? I'm gonna go out on a limb
1999年不离婚
and say no divorces in '99!
但你的离婚手续还没办好
But your divorce isn't even final yet.
1999年只离一次婚
Just the one divorce in '99!
我今年要过得很快乐
Y'know what, I am gonna be happy this year.
我要让自己快乐
I am gonna make myself happy.
你要我们回避吗
Do you want us to leave the room, or?
我每天都要做一件  从没做过的事
Everyday I am gonna do one thing that I haven't done before.
朋友们  这就是我的新年愿望
That my friends is my New Year's resolution.
好棒的愿望
Ooh! That's a good one!
我的愿望是开商用飞机
Mine is to pilot a commercial jet.
这个也很棒  菲比
That's good one too, Pheebs.
你只用找一飞机
Now all you have to do is find a planeload of people
新年愿望是坠机身亡的人
who's resolution is to plummet to their deaths.
也许你的愿望应该是不取笑朋友
Maybe your resolution should be not make fun of your friends,
尤其是很快会免费
especially the ones who may soon
用自己的飞机载你去欧洲的人
be flying you to Europe for free on their own plane.
她开飞机的几率
She has a better chance of sprouting wings
比你不取笑我们还要高
and flying up your nose than you do of not making fun of us.
我愿意赌五十块
In fact, I'll bet you 50 bucks
你不可能一年不取笑我们
that you can't go the whole year without making fun of us.
干脆一星期好了
Eh, y'know what, better yet? A week.
我赌了  哥们
I'll take that bet my friend.
输我那五十块
And you know what, paying me the 50 bucks
就可以当作你的"每日新鲜事"
could be the "new thing you do that day!"
就从现在开始
And it starts right now!
我的新年愿望是学会弹吉他
All right my New Year's resolution is to learn how to play the guitar.
真的吗  为什么
Really?! How come?
我的简历上列了一堆特殊专长
Well, y'know those special skills I have listed on my resume?
我希望有一项是真的
I would love it if one of those was true.
你要我教你吗  我是个很好的老师
Do you want me to teach you? I'm a great teacher.
真的吗  你教过谁
Really? Who-who have you taught?
我教过自己  我很喜欢自己
Well, I taught me and I love me.
太好了  谢谢你  菲比
Yeah that'd be great! Thanks Pheebs!
瞧  布莱尔忘了拿走眼镜
Op, look! Blaire forgot her glasses!
她需要这副眼镜
And she's gonna be really needing these
来盯住男朋友
to keep an eye on that boyfriend,
听说他需要把订书机收在收屉里
who, from I hear, needs to keep his stapler in his desk drawer,
你们懂我的意思吧
if you know what I'm talking about.
瑞秋  或许你的愿望应该是别那么八卦
Hey Rach, maybe your resolution should be to umm, gossip less.
什么  我哪有八卦
What? I don't gossip!
或许我偶尔会发现一些事
Well, maybe sometimes I find out things
或听到一些事  然后转述出去
or I hear something and I pass that information on
这就像一种公共服务  并不代表我很八卦
y'know kinda like a public service, it doesn't mean I'm a gossip.
你们会说新闻主播八卦吗
I mean, would you call Ted Kopel a gossip?
如果他说同事
Well if Ted Kopel talked about his coworkers
隆胸失败的话  我会的
botched boob jobs, I would.
她隆成这样耶
What? They were like this!
-那就明天见  -好的
- I'll see you tomorrow. - Okay!
我刚才约那个女生出去
I just asked that girl out.
-厉害  -厉害啊
- Nice! - Nice!! Yeah!
这算是你今天的新鲜事吗
Is that part of your resolution, your new thing for today?
没错  你们看
Yes it is. See.
伊丽莎白·宏恩斯瓦哥(意为欺骗)
Elizabeth Hornswoggle?
对
That's right, uh,
伊丽莎白·宏恩斯瓦哥
Elizabeth Hornswoggle.
宏恩斯瓦哥
Horn-swoggle.
你没事吧  钱德勒  这名字好笑吗
You okay Chandler? Is there something funny about that name?
不  我只是觉得好像在哪儿听过
No. No, I just think that maybe I-I'd heard it somewhere before.
是吗  在哪里听过
Oh really! Where?
我打赌一定是个很好笑的地方
Somewhere funny I'd bet!
知道吗  我约了伊丽莎白·宏恩斯瓦哥
Oh-oh, guess what? I-I have a date with Elizabeth Hornswoggle.
宏恩斯瓦哥  你一定难受死了
Hornswoggle?  Ooh, this must be killing you.
-待会见  -再见
- All right, see you later. - See ya!
-菲比  我准备好上第一节课了  -好的
- All right Pheebs, I am ready for my first lesson. - Okay.
不行  不能碰吉他
Oh no-no-no, you don't touch the guitar!
-先练手  再练琴  -好的
- First you learn here, then you learn here. - Umm, okay.
第一课  和弦
Okay, lesson one: chords.
我不知道这些和弦的真正名称
Now, I don't know the actual names of the chords
不过我照手势
but umm, I-I-I made up names
帮它们取了名字
for the way my hand looks while I'm doing them.
所以这是熊爪
So then, this is Bear Claw.
火鸡腿
Okay, umm, Turkey Leg
还有老太太
and Old Lady.
真是有趣的吉他教学方式
What an interesting approach to guitar instruction.
有些人可能会觉得好笑  我觉得很普通
Y'know some might find it amusing, I myself find it regular.
各位  瑞秋今天很乖
Hey everybody, Rachel was so good today.
她完全没有八卦
She didn't gossip at all.
没错  即使我发现
I didn't! Even when I found out...
好吧
umm, all right,
我发现了某人的某事
well let's just say I found out something about someone
但是呢  我就是不说
and let's just say she's gonna keep it.
菲比  快看
Hey, Pheebs! Check-check this out.
你搞定老太太了
Ooh, you nailed the Old Lady!
我觉得我进步了
Yeah listen so, I thought I was getting better,
今天回家的路上我就去了吉他店
so on my way home today I stopped by this guitar store and...
你在店里有碰吉他吗
Did you, did you touch any of the guitars while you were there?
有吗
Did you?!
没有
No.
手给我
Give me your hands.
琴弦
Strings.
手给我  拨片
Gimme it! Pick.
-你想学吉他吗  -想啊
－ Do you want to learn to play guitar? － Yes!
那就不要碰吉他
Then don't touch one!!
-嗨  本  -莫妮卡姑姑
- Hi Ben! - Auntie Monica!!
罗斯穿皮裤
Ross is wearing leather pants!
没有人看见罗斯穿皮裤吗
Does nobody else see that Ross is wearing leather pants?
谁来说句话吧
Someone comment on the pants!
很帅气啊
I think they're very nice.
我很喜欢
I really like them a lot.
我想说的不是这个
That's not what I had in mind!
罗斯这种人通常不穿这种裤子
See, people like Ross don't generally wear these types of pants.
这种裤子很紧
You see, they're very tight.
也许可以就这个评论一下
Maybe there's something in that area.
非常好看
They are really good.
在哪里买的
Where did you get them.
我还没做今天的新鲜事
Oh see, I-I needed a new thing for today
我路过这家皮衣店  一直觉得味道很好
and there's this leather store I go by that always smells so good
我心想
and I thought to myself,
我从来没买过
"Wow, I never owned a really
一条很香的皮裤
good smelling pair of pants before."
拜托啦
Oh come on!!
说实话  你们觉得怎样
Okay, seriously, what do you think?
看起来像变态
You look like a freak.
难看死了
Awful, absolutely awful.
你在干什么
What are you, what are you doing?
这是我的新年愿望
It's my New Year's resolution!
把我儿子弄瞎吗
What, to blind my child?
不  是多拍些我们的相片
No! To take more pictures of all of us together.
这是最好的愿望
I mean I really think it's the best resolution
大家都会喜欢的
because everyone will enjoy the pictures.
大家也都会喜欢我的演奏
Well, everyone will enjoy my music as well.
天哪  这条裤子热死了
My God! These pants are burning up!
天哪  她现在靠过来
Oh come on, she wants to snuggle now!
是想让我死吗
What is she trying to kill me?
这里面跟火山一样
It's like a volcano in here!
-你热吗  -不
- Are you hot? - No.
那就是我一个人觉得热了
Okay, it must just be me then.
那是裤子跟沙发磨擦的声音
That was just the pants on the couch.
可以借用一下洗手间吗
Umm, hey, do you, do you mind if I use your bathroom?
-请便  -谢谢
- No, go ahead. - Thanks.
-我最喜欢的部分要开始了  -来了
- Hey, my favorite part is coming up! - 'Kay!
完蛋了
Oh my God!
老虎  恐龙  冰山
Tiger! Dragon! Iceberg!!
乔瑟夫  你昨晚有练习吗
Joseph, did you even study at all last night?
我有啊
Yes! Yes, I did.
那就把冰山做出来
Then do Iceberg!
升G调
G-sharp.
G-sharp?
你偷学了和弦真正的名字吗
Have you been studying the real names of the chords?
有吗  我的天哪
Have you? Oh my God!
怎样  我又没有碰吉他
What?! I didn't touch a guitar!
但是你质疑我的教学方式
No, but you're questioning my method!
我不是质疑  菲比  我根本就觉得很蠢
No, I'm not questioning it, Phoebe, I'm saying it's stupid!
干什么
What?!
谢谢
Thank you.
我其他的学生  可不觉得我很蠢
Y'know none of my other student thought I was stupid.
你就只教过你自己一个学生
Your other student, was you!
知道吗  也许你需要再加把劲
Yeah, well, y'know maybe you just need to try a little harder!
也许我需要请个真正的老师
Maybe I need to try a real teacher!
看  安迪·库珀
Right here! Here! Andy Cooper,
教弹吉他  看
he teaches guitar and look
这里还有他和小朋友的合照
ooh, there's a nice picture of him with a little kid
小朋友拿着吉他
and the kid's got a guitar!!!!!!
行啊
Fine!
你去跟你的专业老师学
You go learn from your qualified instructor!
等大家听腻了《坏小子李洛布朗》
But don't come crying to me when everyone's sick and tired
你可别哭着来找我
of hearing you play Bad, Bad Leroy Brown!!
全城最坏的坏小子
"Baddest man in the whole damn town."
行啊  你也向着他
Oh, fine! Take his side!
我等不及和你在一起
I can't wait to be with you!
罗斯一接走本  我马上溜到你那边去
I'll sneak over as soon as Ross picks up Ben.
我就跟瑞秋讲
I'll just tell Rachel
我要去洗几小时衣服
I'm gonna be doing laundry for a couple of hours.
"洗衣服"  我的新绰号吗
Laundry. Huh. Is that my new nickname?
你知道你的新绰号  大先生
Y'know what your nickname is, Mr. Big...
-喂  -乔伊  我是罗斯  我需要帮忙
- Hello? - Joey, it's Ross! I need some help!
钱德勒不在
Uhh, Chandler's not here.
你可以帮我
Well, you can help me!
-好吧  -我在伊丽莎白的浴室里
- Okay. - Listen, I'm in Elizabeth's bathroom...
厉害
Nice!
不是  我觉得皮裤很热
No, I-I got really hot in my leather pants
就进来脱掉  结果它一定是遇汗缩水
so I took them off but they must have shrunk from the-
或是我的腿因热膨胀
the sweat or-or-or my legs expanded from the heat.
我现在穿不回去了  乔伊  穿不上了
Look, I-I can't put them back on. Joey, I can't!
这个情况挺严重的
Oh. That is quite a situation.
你有粉之类的东西吗
Uh, do you see any like, powder?
有  我有爽身粉
Powder! Yeah! Yeah, I have powder!
很好  在腿上撒些粉
Good-good, okay, sprinkle some of that on your legs,
可以吸汗
it'll absorb some of the moisture
然后就能把裤子穿回去了
and then you can get your pants back up.
好  等一下
Yeah, okay, hold on!
裤子还是拉不上来
They're not coming on man.
你找得到  凡士林吗
Umm, do you see any-oh, Vaseline?
我找到乳液  我有乳液  乳液行吗
Ohh, I-I see lotion, I have lotion! Will that work?
行  把它涂在腿上
Yeah, sure, throw some of that on there.
等一下
Hold on.
裤子还是拉不上来
They're still, they're still not coming on man
而且乳液和爽身粉糊成了一团
and the lotion and the powder have made a paste!
是嘛
Really?!
什么颜色
Uhh, what color is it?
什么颜色有差别吗
What difference does that make?!
如果跟裤子的颜色一样
Well, I'm just-if the paste matches the pants,
你就糊一条假裤子
you can make yourself a pair of paste pants
她就看不出来了
and she won't know the difference!
乔伊  你有空吗
Joey, do you have a minute?
哥们  我该怎么...
Dude, what am I gonna...
瑞秋来了  祝你好运  让我知道结果
Uh, Rachel's here, so good luck man, let me know how it works out.
乔伊  我遇到了天大的问题
Oh, Joey, I have such a problem!
你来得正好
Oh well, you're timing couldn't be better.
我正在到处救火
I am putting out fires all over the place.
好的  乔伊  我得告诉你一件事
Okay. Okay. Okay. Joey, I have got to tell you something!
什么事
What-what is it, what is it?
天哪  这件事太大了
Oh my God, it's so huge,
你得保证不说出去
but you just have to promise me that you cannot tell anyone.
不要  我不想知道
Oh no, no-no-no-no! I don't want to know!
你绝对想知道  太不可思议了
Yes! Yes! Yes, you do want to know! This is unbelievable!
我不在乎  瑞秋  我已经厌倦了
I don't care, Rach! Look, I am tired of being the guy
知道所有秘密却不能说
who knows all the secrets but can't tell anyone!
什么秘密  你知道什么秘密
What? What secrets? You know secrets? What are they?
你不该八卦的
And you're not supposed to be gossiping!!
我知道  但这件事我憋不住
I know, I know! I just can't keep this one in,
我刚才拿起电话
so I pick up the phone...
我不听
I'm not listening to you!
罗斯  你进去很久了
Ross, umm, you've been in there for a long time.
我开始有点害怕了
I'm starting to get kinda freaked out.
好  我要出去了
All right, I'm coming out.
你可以把灯关掉吗
Hey, can you turn the lights off.
不  灯就开着吧
No, let's just leave the lights on.
我的天哪
Oh my God!
我出了一点状况
I had a problem.
菲比
Hey, Pheebs?
我没资格跟你说话
I can't talk to you!
我连黄页广告都登不起
I don't have a fancy ad in the Yellow Pages!
听我说  菲比
Look, Pheebs, I just,
我是来道歉的
I wanna apologize for,
我不该说你的教法很蠢
for saying that your method was stupid
我想重新拜你为师
and-and maybe ask you to be my teacher again.
我保证
And-and I promise,
在你说可以之前  我绝对不碰吉他
I won't touch a guitar until you say I'm ready.
-我真的可以了吗  -是的
- You really think I'm ready? - Uh-huh!
酷毙了
Wow! Cool!
-至少那个和弦弹对了吧  -不对
- Was the chord at least right beofre... - No!
我的天
Oh my God!
我们听说了你裤子的事  真惨
We heard about your pants, I'm so sorry.
今年应该是开心的一年
This year was supposed to be great!
才第二天我就成了
But, it's only the second day and I'm a loser
穿不合身的皮裤的倒霉鬼
with stupid leather pants that don't even fit!
你不是倒霉鬼
No. No, you're not a loser.
你们看我
Look at me!
你看
Hey, hey, look.
罗斯  本画了你的画像
Look Ross, Ben drew a picture of you!
你是牛仔
Huh? You're-you're a cowboy!
因为我穿皮裤了
Oh, be-because of the leather pants.
看见没  本不觉得你是倒霉鬼
See? Ben doesn't think you're a loser,
他觉得你是牛仔  很棒吧
he thinks you're a cowboy! Now that's something.
真的很棒  太酷了
Yeah! That really is something; that's really cool.
牛仔哥
Howdy partner!
也许我应该再去买一条
Maybe I should get another pair!
知道吗  他们有一些
Ooh, y'know, they-they had some
侧边有流苏的
with fringe all down the sides.
我去跟本说晚安
I'm gonna go kiss Ben goodnight.
他居然觉得我是牛仔
I can't believe he thinks I'm a cowboy.
我会是个优秀的牛仔
I would make a good cowboy.
好了  既然没事了
Okay, now that everything's wrapped up here,
我要去洗衣服了
I think I'm, I'm gonna go do my laundry.
我也是  如果这一件脏了的话  脏了
Oh yeah, me too. Y'know if this shirt is dirty. Yep.
我也走了
Okay, I'm gonna go too.
去机场
I'm gonna go to the airport.
我想如果我一直在那里守着
I figure if I hang around there long enough,
总会发现没人管的飞机
someone's bound to leave one of those planes unattended.
-祝你好运  亲爱的  -再见
- Good luck, honey! - Bye!
-乔伊  记得我要说的那件大事吗  -不
－ Joey, remember that big thing I was gonna tell you about? - Oh, no!
我不会告诉你  但如果你自己发现了
I'm not gonna tell you, but if you found out on your own,
那就没关系  我们就可以讨论了对吧
that would be okay and then we could talk about it. Right?
那样就不是秘密了
Well, then it wouldn't be a secret.
的确没关系
So yeah, that would be okay. Yeah. Yeah!
乔伊  麻烦你到钱德勒的卧室
Hey uh Joe, would you mind going over to Chandler's bedroom
把我借给他的书拿回来好吗
and get that book back that he borrowed from me?
现在  你要我现在去吗
Now? You want me to go over there now?
你知道了什么吗
Do you know something?
我或许知道什么
I might know something.
我也是
I might know something too.
你知道什么
What's the thing you know?
你先说我才能说
Oh no, I can't tell you until you tell me what you know.
我不能说
I can't tell you what I know.
那我也不能说
Well then I can't tell you what I know.
那好吧
Okay, fine.
你才不知道
You don't know!
不如我现在就去
All right, how about I go over there
钱德勒的房间
and I will walk into Chandler's bedroom
就可以看到我以为自己知道的事
and I will see that thing that I think that I know
的确是那件我以为自己知道的事
is actually the thing that I think that I know!
你知道
You know!!!!
你也知道
And you know!!!
对  我知道
Yeah, I know!!!!
钱德勒和莫妮卡
Chandler and Monica?!!
真叫人不敢相信
Oh, this is unbelievable!!
你知道多久了
How long have you known?
太久了  天哪  瑞秋
Too long! Oh my God, Rach,
我早就想找人说了  我都快疯了
I've been dying to talk to someone about this for so long!
你不能告诉别人
Listen, listen, we can't say anything about this to anybody,
他们两个好紧张  听着
they're so weird about that! Listen...
下雨了  我不想在下雨天飞  所以就回来了
It's raining. I don't want to fly in the rain. So...
我要去雨中漫步
Oh, I am going to go for a walk in the rain.
我也要
Ohhh, yeah, me too.
真怪  他们肯定有一腿
That's weird.  I bet they're doing it.
够了  我受不了了  受不了了
Okay, look. I can't take it anymore. I can't take it anymore.
你赢了  好吗  拿去
So you win. Okay? Here.
菲比  开飞机吗  不如开太空船
Pheebs. Flying a jet? Better make it a spaceship...
回你的星球去吧
...so you can get back to your home planet!
罗斯  今天有你的电话
And Ross phone call for you today.
汤姆·琼斯想要回他的裤子
Tom Jones. He wants his pants back!
姓"骗子"
And Hornswoggle?
你跟《弗雷格尔星》里的角色约会吗
What, are you dating a character from Fraggle Rock?